rockettab.com 2016-01-22

# Rocket Tab | Privacy Policy

Rich River Media’s application RocketTab 2.0 has been certified by the TRUSTe’s Trusted Download Program signifying that the RocketTab application has been tested TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe’s TDP program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe’s mission is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding the RocketTab application, please contact us at Rich River Media, LLC at 26895 Aliso Creek Road, Aliso Viejo, CA 92656 or by email at contact@rockettab.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](https://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&softwareProgramId=502&sealid=112).

Trusted Download certification does not cover other applications such as mobile versions, Facebook or Twitter apps.

Rich River Media LLC (“Rich River Media” or “we”) respects the privacy of its users (“you”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is to inform you about how we intend to collect, use, disclose and protect your information that is received in connection with this site (the “Site”) or any services, applications and/or software provided through the Site (collectively, the “Services”). We seek to handle your information in a manner that complies fully with the privacy principles and requirements under all applicable United States federal and state privacy legislation and regulations. Rich River Media may modify this policy from time to time, and the changes will be posted here.

### Acceptance

This privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to Rich River Media’s Terms of Service. THE USE OF THE SITE OR ANY OF THE SERVICES CONSTITUTES THE ACCEPTANCE OF BOTH TERMS OF SERVICE AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of either document, please discontinue using the Site and the Services.

### Information Collected And How We Use It

You always remain in control of the information you provide to Rich River Media. We may collect two types of information about visitors: personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, email address, etc.) which you have voluntarily submitted to us, and aggregate information (such as information about how many visitors log on to our sites, the pages they access, etc.).

In general, you can visit the Site and use the Services without telling us who you are or revealing personal information about yourself. We may collect, maintain and use personal information you have voluntarily submitted to contact you, including via email, to respond to your comments or requests for information, or to contact you if needed in the course of providing information about our services that you may have requested. To better meet your needs, we may supplement the information we collect with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes.

Rich River Media collects data to identify what operating system and browser our users are using. This allows us to ensure our application is working successfully, and notify our users of any pending technology changes. Rich River Media also collects data on websites you have visited including the contents of encrypted web pages and the searches you have conducted in order to show you the most relevant content and ads. These items above are not combined with any user identification parameters or any other personally identifiable information. The information is also never shared with any 3rd parties. If you would like us to not capture this information, please uninstall RocketTab.

### Data Sharing And Transfer

Rich River Media will not trade, sell or share your personal information for use by any third party without your consent, unless required by law or as disclosed to you when the information is collected. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information based on the good faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate to: (a) protect and defend the rights or property of Rich River Media, or (b) act in urgent circumstances to protect the safety or security of the public or of users of the Site or Services.

Your personal information will generally be stored in our databases, which are located in the United States. Our policy is to ensure that your information is always granted the same level of protection no matter where it is stored. In the event that Rich River Media is involved in a transaction such as a merger, stock purchase or sale, or sale of substantially all of the its assets, your personal information may be transferred to the other party in such transaction.

### Use Of Your Personally Identifiable Information

Upon our collection of your personally identifiable information, we may use such personally identifiable information internally, separately or in combination with pre-existing information, for the following purposes:

  * To provide any requested services;
  * To troubleshoot problems with the Site, or any Services, as requested;
  * To customize your experience on the Site and with the Services;
  * To enforce our Terms of Service; or
  * To contact you with more information about us and our services.

### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Browser Cookies

As with many other sites, the Site may use “cookies” or other technologies to help us deliver content specific to your interests, to process your inquiries or requests, and/or to analyze your visiting patterns. Cookies, by themselves, will not be used by us to disclose your individual identity. This information identifies your browser, but not you, to our servers when you visit the Site. If you want to disable the use of cookies or remove them at any time from your computer, you can disable or delete them using your browser (consult your browser’s “help” menu to learn how to delete cookies). We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our Site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

We may also collect data by using “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs” or similar means (collectively, “pixel tags”) that allow us to know when you visit the Site. We potentially can combine machine ID with a user’s IP address when installing, uninstalling or activating the Service. Through pixel tags, we obtain non-personal information or aggregate information (i.e., your IP address, the areas of the Site you visit, your operating system, your browser version, the URL you came from and the pages you visited while you were using the Site and Services) which can be used to enhance your online experience and understand traffic patterns.

### Updating Your Information

We believe that choice in how and when you are contacted is key to customer satisfaction, so we offer several ways for you to update your contact information:

  1. You may contact us at [contact@rockettab.com](mailto:contact@rockettab.com) for any inquiry or request regarding our privacy policy or the handling of your personal information.
  2. You may unsubscribe to any of our e-mails by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any e-mail message.

  3. You also may write to us directly if you wish to: (a) update or delete your contact information; or (b) request that we cease sending you promotional or other information via mail or e-mail. Such written requests should be sent to Rich River Media at the address below.

### Third-Party Companies

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and these third-party companies may collect certain anonymous information when you visit the Site or use any of the Services. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits and use in order to provide advertisements about goods and service likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies may use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### No Error-Free Performance

Rich River Media does not guarantee error-free performance. Rich River Media will always try its best to protect its user and data privacy; however, it may not catch all unintended privacy issues. Rich River Media is not responsible for any damages, including incidental, consequential, or punitive damages, relating to the practices described in this policy.

### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services as part of installation with the Services. These third party services have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Site and the Services and welcome any feedback about these sites, partners, or services.

### Special Notice To California Residents

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared personal information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of Personal Information shared. If you are a California resident and wish to make such a request, please send an e-mail to [contact@rockettab.com](mailto:contact@rockettab.com) and include the phrase “California Privacy Request” in the subject line, and provide us with your name, address and e-mail address. We will respond to you within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. The Site and Services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

###  Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through the Site or Services and not to information collected offline.

### International Users

You agree that any claim, action or proceeding arising out of this Privacy Policy, or your use of the Site or the Services, shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the United States and the State of California, without regard to principles of conflict of laws. Any claim, action or proceeding related to this Privacy Policy will be resolved exclusively in the state or federal courts located in the State of California and you consent to the jurisdiction of those courts. If you are accessing the Site or Services from outside of the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. Your use of the Site and the Services indicates your consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities anywhere across the world and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our Users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the posted Privacy Policy when you visit the Site or use any of the Services to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. We will also attempt to take proactive steps to notify you of material changes to our Site and/or Services by displaying messaging on the application itself. Your continued use of the Site and/or the Services means you accept the updated Privacy Policy.

### Contacting Us
